(Howard:)Check it out. Press release. From NASA.
Ahem. "Expedition 31 will launch this spring
to the International Space Station.
(Raj:)Crew members will include
Commander Tom'Tombo' Johnson...
...astronaut Mike'Supernova' Novacelik,
and payload specialist Howard Wolowitz."
(Howard:)This is going right into
my synagogue's newsletter.
(Raj:)If you're going to be an astronaut,
you need to pick a cool nickname.
(Howard:)I don't get to.
The other guys have to give it to me.
(Raj:)Oh. If I had one,
it would be Brown Dynamite.
(Howard:)Are you not listening to me? The other
astronauts have to give you your nickname.
(Raj:)Are you not looking at me?
I am Brown Dynamite.
(Raj:)Why do you put six sugars
in your coffee?
(Leonard:)Because the cafeteria doesn't offer
Iittle packets of methamphetamine.
- Emergency drill night last night, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- How'd you do?
- I'll tell you exactly how he did.